# **Guy-Frederic Wulff Software Engineer**

Miami, FL. (786)832-5877
US Citizen
guyfredw@outlook.com
linkedin.com/in/guyfrederic-wulff
github.com/guyfredw
guyfredw.github.io

Full Stack Developer with 3 years experience building scalable web applications. I have built applications from the ground-up acting in several different roles in the development process such as tester, scrum master and developer due to my background in Software Development, Information systems and Project Management.

# **Education**

## The University of Tampa

BS, Management Information Systems (Cum Laude)

# **Skills**

- JavaScript
- Python
- Java
- React.js
- Node.js
- Express.js

- MongoDB
- Ct
- React Native
- Git
- Spring
- PostgreSQL

- SQL Server
- DevOps
- Django
- Angular.js
- Jenkins

# **Projects**

# **Proposal Tracker**

- React and React Native application
- Deploying backend in Azure and AWS using Cosmos DB and DynamoDB, Serverless Function and Lambda Function
- Building REST API with Node.js

#### Medical Clinic Management Application

• React and React Native Application. Java Spring RESTful API with MongoDB as Database.

## **Social Media Application**

- Built a RESTful API using Django while using object-oriented programming to create the models and the relationship of the resources
- Full-stack social media application created with React, HTML, CSS, React, Python and Django

# **Scrum Application**

- Using the git workflow, we created branches for new features, and issued/reviewed pull requests to integrate them in the main branch to keep a consistent application and development process
- Worked with three other developers to create a full-stack web application built with React, React-Bootstrap, Express.js, Mongoose, and MongoDB.

# **Professional Experience**

#### **XIOTEN,** Developer

February 2020-December 2020

- Lead Developer for Azure Serverless Function, Kafka Consumer and Producer.
- Perform peer code review and participate in developer meetings to share and raise questions about the technology challenges / achievements.
- Designed and implemented the REST API for the UI screen
- Worked on Front End/User Interface (UI) Technologies like using HTML4/5, CSS2/3, DHTML, JavaScript, jQuery, React JS, JWT, Bootstrap Framework, Modernizer JS, AJAX, JSON.
- Worked closely with the Business Analyst and Db developer to identify with the Business requirements and to implement the functionality of the applications.
- Experience in all phases of software development life cycle like Requirement Analysis, Design, Development and Unit testing of applications.
- Hosting applications with the AWS Cloud.
- Develop CI/CD pipeline using Code Pipeline, Code Commit and Code Deploy.

# **Guy-Frederic Wulff Software Engineer**

Miami, FL. (786)832-5877
US Citizen
guyfredw@outlook.com
linkedin.com/in/guyfrederic-wulff

github.com/guyfredw guyfredw.github.io

- Worked on Server less services (Azure Functions) created and configured HTTP Triggers services and Timer/Schedule Services using Azure Functions
- Implemented Azure Storage, Azure SQL Services and developing Azure Web roles

#### **XIOTEN,** Developer

June 2019-November 2019

- Worked on an Agile (Scrum) Development Team to deliver and maintain Web applications.
- Involved in Design and Development of the end user specifications, evaluate and Customization of the web Application.
- Implemented various screens for the front end using React.js
- Communicate with the client to understand the requirement of the website, Wrote the user stories and implemented and tested the functionality.
- Created Responsive Designs (Mobile/Tablet/Desktop) using HTML&CSS, Bootstrap.

## CITADIER, Junior Front-end Developer

June 2018-December 2018

- Design, develop and test HTML5, CSS3, Bootstrap, JavaScript, jQuery and ReactJS
- Maintained states in the stores and dispatched the actions using redux
- Worked with backend engineers to optimize existing API calls to create efficiencies by deprecating unneeded API calls. Called the Restful web services calls for POST, PUT, DELETE and GET methods.
- Team up and communicate with the players on the progress milestones during the stand-up scrum meetings.
- Used JIRA as the bug tracking system to track and maintain the history of bugs/issues on everyday basis.
- Interacted with Testing Team, Scrum Masters and Business Analysts for fixing of Issues.

## LotoLakay S.A.

Port-au-Prince, Haiti

Summer Intern – Shadow Experience

June 2018-August 2018

• Worked in the development of a project, more specifically determining project requirements and specifications to be reviewed by management. Learned about the challenges and opportunities of working with a start-up